- Raj?
- No way, Jose.
- But I can't do it. I can't see anything.
- It's all right.
(Howard:)Wireless mini-cam
and Bluetooth headset.
(Howard:)We'll be your eyes.
- Fine.
- One more thing.
(Howard:)This is a sub-sonic impact sensor.
(Howard:)If Sheldon gets out of bed
and starts to walk...
...this will register it
and send a signal to the laptop.
(Howard:)At that point, based on the geography of
the apartment and the speed of Sheldon...
(Howard:)...you'll have seven seconds to get out,
glasses or no glasses.
(Leonard:)Won't my footsteps set it off?
(Howard:)No. You'll be on your hands and knees.
(Howard:)Now, you'll need to get the sensor
close to Sheldon's room.
(Leonard:)How do I carry it
if I'm on my hands and knees?
HOWARD:
Stay low.
(Howard:)Bear left.
(Howard:)- Now keep true.
- What?
- It means go straight.
- Then just say, "Go straight."
You don't say, "Go straight," when you're
giving bearings. You say, "Keep true."